<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Credenz \'17</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="action_privPolicy">Privacy Policy</string>

    <string name="receipt_header"><u><b>RECEIPT</b></u></string>
    <string name="receipt_events_header"><u><b>Events:</b></u></string>
    <string name="receipt_name_header"><u><b>Participants:</b></u></string>
    <string name="receipt_category_header"><u><b>Category:</b></u></string>
    <string name="receipt_college_header"><u><b>College:</b></u></string>
    <string name="receipt_reg_header"><u><b>Registration Id:</b></u></string>

    <string name="no_of_receipts">com.pisb.credenz17.receiptsCount</string>

    <string name="contact_us"><b>Contact Us:</b>\nRajat Paliwal: +919890225872
    \nStavan Shah: +919930317212</string>

    <string name="home_screen_text">Visit our website:\nwww.credenz.info</string>

    <string name="help_guidelines">Please read these instructions carefully:
        \n\n<b>1.</b> Click on the \'+\' button to add an e-Receipt
        \n\n<b>2.</b> In case of an offline registration where you received a paper receipt, you will receive
        your registration id for the e-receipt via email.
        \n\n<b>3.</b> Scan the QR to get your receipt immediately, else you can also enter your registration
        ID (present in the system generated e-mail) to generate your e-receipt.
        \n\n<b>4.</b> You can save a maximum of 8 receipts at a time. If you have more,
        please use the e-receipt sent on your registered email address.</string>

    <string name="app_share">This is the official CREDENZ \'17 app.\n\nIt is an
        attempt to make digital receipts available to all our participants. So, once registered,
        do store your receipt(s) here to get rid of paper receipts.\n\n</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_link">https://sites.google.com/view/credenz17-privacy-policy/home</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Roadmap</string>
    <string name="title_activity_webweaver">Web Weaver</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <string name="action_intro">Intro</string>
    <string name="action_rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="action_structure">Structure</string>
    <string name="action_judging">Judging</string>
    <string name="action_contact">Contact</string>

    <string name="event_name_web">Web Weaver</string>


    <!--WEB WEAVER-->
    <string name="web_intro">Think about what happens when you visit a website that is poorly
        designed as opposed to one that is clean, easy-to-use and modern? The look and feel of a
        website is critical to keep visitors engaged online. If you think you can do this, it\'s
        time for you to design such a site. A striking blend of technology, skill and CREATIVITY
        can help you win this competition. Develop a website captivating enough to grab the
        attention of your peers and an experienced panel of judges.\n\n</string>
    <string name="web_rules">1. All teams shall have to get their own laptops on the day of the competition. It is advisable to get a
high speed data card (even though net connection will be provided), for your convenience.\n\n
2. A team of maximum 3 is permissible for the event.\n\n
3. The fee for the events is Rs 150/- for non-IEEE members and Rs 120/- for IEEE members per
team.\n\n
4. All the participants should bring receipt and valid I-cards while coming for the contest. A single
team member without an I-card will result in the disqualification of the entire team.\n\n
5. Use of any front end framework is permitted.\n\n
6. You are allowed to use any language but readymade template must not be used.\n\n
7. Wordpress is not allowed.\n\n</string>
    <string name="web_structure"><b><u>1st Round</u></b>\n
1. A problem statement shall be given to the participants online.\n
2. The problem statement shall be released approximately 15 Days prior to
the main event.\n
3. The team should mail the files in zip archive. (All files with understandable documentation.)\n\n
<b><u>2nd Round</u></b>\n
<b>1.</b> The second round shall be conducted at PICT.\n
2. Approximately 10 teams shall be shortlisted.\n
3. The teams shall be given certain add-ons over the pages designed earlier.\n
4. Five add-ons shall be given, specific to the pages designed by the participants.\n\n</string>
    <string name="web_judging">1. Creativity and originality of the design.\n\n
2. Distinct features incorporated in the design.\n\n
3. Navigation through the site, how well the pages are interconnected.\n\n
4. Persuasiveness of the design, the efficiency of the site to give primary
        information on the required theme.\n\n
5. Based on the your Design, UI/UX and Development.\n\n
6. Additional points will be awarded for backend development.\n\n</string>

    <string name="web_coord1">Anurag Kallurwar</string>
    <string name="web_coord1_contact">+91 9405225170</string>
    <string name="web_coord2">Chinmay Shimpi</string>
    <string name="web_coord2_contact">+91 9403192826</string>
    <string name="web_email">webweaver.credenz17@gmail.com</string>


    <!--B-Plan-->
    <string name="bplan_intro">yfdsmfbjsdvjshb</string>
    <string name="bplan_rules">assdfsdfsd</string>
</resources>
