<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Credenz \'17</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="action_privPolicy">Privacy Policy</string>

    <string name="receipt_header"><u><b>RECEIPT</b></u></string>
    <string name="receipt_events_header"><u><b>Events:</b></u></string>
    <string name="receipt_name_header"><u><b>Participants:</b></u></string>
    <string name="receipt_category_header"><u><b>Category:</b></u></string>
    <string name="receipt_college_header"><u><b>College:</b></u></string>
    <string name="receipt_reg_header"><u><b>Registration Id:</b></u></string>

    <string name="no_of_receipts">com.pisb.credenz17.receiptsCount</string>

    <string name="alert_receipt_delete">Do you want to delete the receipt with registration id: %1$s</string>

    <string name="contact_us"><b>Contact Us:</b>\nRajat Paliwal: +919890225872
    \nStavan Shah: +919930317212</string>

    <string name="home_screen_text">Visit our website:\nwww.credenz.info</string>

    <string name="help_guidelines">Please read these instructions carefully:
        \n\n<b>1.</b> Click on the \'+\' button to add an e-Receipt
        \n\n<b>2.</b> In case of an offline registration where you received a paper receipt, you will receive
        your registration id for the e-receipt via email.
        \n\n<b>3.</b> Scan the QR to get your receipt immediately, else you can also enter your registration
        ID (present in the system generated e-mail) to generate your e-receipt.
        \n\n<b>4.</b> You can save a maximum of 8 receipts at a time. If you have more,
        please use the e-receipt sent on your registered email address.</string>

    <string name="app_share">This CREDENZ \'17 official app is here!.\n\nThis year, download our app
        to get all your receipts in one place. Open, scan and save. It\'s that easy. Download the app now!\n\n</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_link">https://sites.google.com/view/credenz17-privacy-policy/home</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Roadmap</string>
    <string name="title_activity_webweaver">Web Weaver</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <string name="action_intro">Intro</string>
    <string name="action_rules">Rules</string>
    <string name="action_structure">Structure</string>
    <string name="action_judging">Judging</string>
    <string name="action_contact">Contact</string>

    <string name="event_name_bplan">B-Plan</string>
    <string name="event_name_wallstreet">Wall Street</string>
    <string name="event_name_clash">Clash</string>
    <string name="event_name_contraption">Contraption</string>
    <string name="event_name_cretronix">Cretronix</string>
    <string name="event_name_croodle">Croodle</string>
    <string name="event_name_mad">Mad Talks</string>
    <string name="event_name_nth">N.T.H.</string>
    <string name="event_name_pixelate">Pixelate</string>
    <string name="event_name_quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="event_name_xodia">Xodia</string>
    <string name="event_name_rc">Reverse Coding</string>
    <string name="event_name_web">Web Weaver</string>
    <string name="event_name_ppt">Paper Presentation</string>
    <string name="event_name_robo">Roboliga</string>
    <string name="event_name_seminar">Seminars</string>
    <string name="event_name_workshops">Workshops</string>
    <string name="event_name_sd">Software Development</string>


    <!--Seminars-->
    <string name="seminar_1">Seminar 1</string>
    <string name="seminar_2">Seminar 2</string>

    <!--Workshops-->
    <string name="workshop1">Workshop 1</string>
    <string name="workshop2">Workshop 2</string>
    <!--WEB WEAVER-->
    <string name="web_intro">Think about what happens when you visit a website that is poorly
        designed as opposed to one that is clean, easy-to-use and modern? The look and feel of a
        website is critical to keep visitors engaged online. If you think you can do this, it\'s
        time for you to design such a site. A striking blend of technology, skill and CREATIVITY
        can help you win this competition. Develop a website captivating enough to grab the
        attention of your peers and an experienced panel of judges.\n\n</string>
    <string name="web_rules">1. All teams shall have to get their own laptops on the day of the competition. It is advisable to get a
high speed data card (even though net connection will be provided), for your convenience.
\n\n2. A team of maximum 3 is permissible for the event.
\n\n3. The fee for the events is Rs 150/- for non-IEEE members and Rs 120/- for IEEE members per
team.
\n\n4. All the participants should bring receipt and valid I-cards while coming for the contest. A single
team member without an I-card will result in the disqualification of the entire team.
\n\n5. Use of any front end framework is permitted.
\n\n6. You are allowed to use any language but readymade template must not be used.
\n\n7. Wordpress is not allowed.\n\n</string>
    <string name="web_structure"><b><u>1st Round</u></b>
\n1. A problem statement shall be given to the participants online.
\n2. The problem statement shall be released approximately 15 Days prior to
the main event.
\n3. The team should mail the files in zip archive. (All files with understandable documentation.)
\n\n2nd Round
\n1. The second round shall be conducted at PICT.
\n2. Approximately 10 teams shall be shortlisted.
\n3. The teams shall be given certain add-ons over the pages designed earlier.
\n4. Five add-ons shall be given, specific to the pages designed by the participants.\n\n</string>
    <string name="web_judging">1. Creativity and originality of the design.
\n\n2. Distinct features incorporated in the design.
\n\n3. Navigation through the site, how well the pages are interconnected.
\n\n4. Persuasiveness of the design, the efficiency of the site to give primary
        information on the required theme.
\n\n5. Based on the your Design, UI/UX and Development.
\n\n6. Additional points will be awarded for backend development.\n\n</string>
    <string name="web_question">
        Design a Website for an Art Gallery Portal with the following features:
        \n\n1. The website must exhibit its facilities to artists and visitors in an interactive and responsive manner.
        \n\n2. The website must provide information about various art galleries around the world.
        \n\n3. The site must present profiles of famous artists along with their major works and masterpieces.
        \n\n4. Judging criteria includes UI/UX of the website, creativity and features that bring out uniqueness.
        \n\n5. The Structure of the site is up to the participant it may contain a single page or multiple pages.
        The participant might also design a section for upcoming art exhibition and Art Festivals.
        Additional Features to enhance your website are welcomed. The presentation must be professional
        with contrast to artistic elements. Images, Videos, GIFs and any other supporting media relevant
        to the subject can be used by the participant.
        \n\nEmail your website in a zip file at webweaver.credenz17@gmail.com.
        \n\nLast date of Submission is 9th September 2017.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="web_coord1">Anurag Kallurwar</string>
    <string name="web_coord1_contact">+91 9405225170</string>
    <string name="web_coord2">Chinmay Shimpi</string>
    <string name="web_coord2_contact">+91 9403192826</string>
    <string name="web_email">webweaver.credenz17@gmail.com</string>



    <!--Roboliga-->
    <string name="robo_intro">Football- The most breath-taking game becomes even more so when it\'s the robots that play the
game! Bring your footballer-bot to the game and become a part of the most attractive events
of Credenz \'17. As an event that surely keeps everyone\'s eyes transfixed on the field, RoboLIGA
does not fail to entertain and teach at the same time. Explore the Robotics-aspect of Credenz and
experience the extravagant thrill as you make your bot wade past the opponent and &#8230;that\'s right –
SCORE!\n\n</string>
    <string name="robo_rules">
1. A maximum of 3 candidates pursuing undergraduate program in their institution are allowed per
team.
\n\n2. Registration fee is Rs.200/- per team for Non-IEEE members and Rs.160/- per team for IEEE
members.
\n\n3. Teams can register at the desk put up in various colleges in and around Pune. Teams can also
register at the registration desk on the day of the event, at least an hour prior to the event.
\n\n4. ROBOT LIMITATIONS
\nMaximum robot dimensions: 30cm x 30 cm x 30 cm.
\nMaximum weight 3.5 kg.
\n\n5. Power specifications:
\n- Max Voltage: 12V (Normal Operation).
\n- 18 V (Momentary surge on load only) allowed three times in a match.
\n- The robot cannot split into two independent parts.
\n- Robot should be manually controlled.
\n- No weapons (blades, spikes) of any kind should be attached onto the robot.
\n- The participants are allowed to use any number of actuators.
\n- Max Current 5A.
\n\n6. There should be no intentional damage done to the other robot by means of attacking wires,
wheels, motors etc.
\n\n7. Any damage to the field or to the opposing robot would result in immediate
disqualification of the team.
\n\n8. All the participants should bring receipt and valid I-cards while coming for the contest. No one
without I-card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified.
\n\n9. If any changes are done in the competition pattern, they will be uploaded on the website. For any further information keep checking the website.\n\n</string>
    <string name="robo_structure">
1. The duration of each match will be 8 minutes (i.e. two halves, each of 4 minutes duration). A 30-
seconds break will be given after half time during which the teams will be allowed to attend to their
robots.
\n\n2. Each match will be a one-on-one match between two similar teams selected randomly. For scoring
system, refer to Judging Tab.
\n\n3. The team with the highest number of points is the winner of the match. In case of a tie, a penalty
shootout will be held, details of which will be announced at the time of the event.
\n\n4. The field will be subjected to changes after the elimination rounds. The field design for final rounds
will be revealed on the website before the final rounds.
\n\n5. The teams will be short-listed for final rounds on the basis of their score in the elimination round.
In final rounds, matches will be one-on-one with a different scoring system as in the Judging tab.
\n\n6. A yellow card will be flashed on each hand touch after the first one. A maximum of three such
cards will add up to a red card i.e. Disqualification.
\n\n7. Losing teams may re-register to participate again in the elimination round. Registration fees
would be Rs.150/- for this case. (Organizers reserve the rights to close the re-registrations at any
point of time).
\n\n8. Organizers have the authority to disqualify any team for misconduct or disorderly behaviour.
This team would not be allowed to re-register.
\n\n9. Organizers reserve the rights to make changes to the field design at any time without prior
notification. Participants are requested to refer to the website regularly for any such changes.
\n\n10. Organizers\' decisions will be final and binding to all.\n\n</string>
    <string name="robo_judging">
A. Elimination round:
\nI. Goal from inner circle: +20 points.
\nII. Goal from between inner circle and half line: +40 points
\nIII. Goal from beyond half line: +60 points
\nIV. Negative points for Yellow Cards and fouls.
\nV. Disqualification on Red Card.
\nNote: This may change at the time of the event
\n\nB. Final round: To be declared on the website after elimination round. \n\n</string>
    <string name="robo_question">Web Weaver Question Statement</string>
    <string name="robo_coord1">Pranav Agrawal</string>
    <string name="robo_coord1_contact">+91 9765229963</string>
    <string name="robo_coord2">Utsav Guru</string>
    <string name="robo_coord2_contact">+91 9749983775</string>
    <string name="robo_email">roboliga.credenz17@gmail.com</string>





    <!--Clash-->
    <string name="clash_intro">A C/C++ coding competition held in high regard for the conceptual challenges it brings to a coder\'s
mind. \'C\'-LASH beckons all the programmers, amateur and experienced alike to
participate and enhance their coding skills! Utterly professional yet non-compromising on coding-
fun, CLASH tests you for your speed, logic and checks if you have the right outlook towards a
problem. So \'compile\' yourself and join this national-level coding combat in Credenz \'17!\n\n</string>
    <string name="clash_structure">1. There will be TWO rounds per group:· Elimination Round (MCQ\'s Round)
· Coding Round (Final Round)
\n\n2. Owing to the vast nature of the programming language, the event will be conducted in two
categories, Junior Level and Senior Level.
\n\n3. Teams can register at the registration desk on the day of the event, 1 hour prior to the event.
Teams can also register at desks put up at various colleges in Pune.
\n\n4. The competition will test the participant\'s programming skills and knowledge of C/C++.
\n\n5. The Second Round structure will be declared on the spot.\n\n</string>
    <string name="clash_rules">1. A maximum of 2 candidates pursuing undergraduate program at their institution are allowed per
team.
\n\n2. Registration fee is Rs. 100/- per team for Non-IEEE members and Rs. 80/- per team for IEEE
members.
\n\n3. All the participants should bring receipt and valid I-cards while coming for the contest. A
participant without an I-card will NOT be allowed for the contest and the respective team will be
disqualified.\n\n</string>
    <string name="clash_judging">1. The competition will test participants programming skills and knowledge of C/C++.
\n\n2. Time and cost efficiency of the code.\n\n</string>
    <string name="clash_coord1">Abizer Lokhandwala</string>
    <string name="clash_coord1_contact">+91 9552645237</string>
    <string name="clash_coord2">Akash Bachkar</string>
    <string name="clash_coord2_contact">+91 9561541085</string>
    <string name="clash_email">clash.credenz17@gmail.com</string>


    <!--MAD Talks-->
    <string name="mad_intro">Ever had an idea or a thought deemed absurd by society? Here at MAD talks, we appreciate your
crazy ideas.
\nMAD talks gives you a platform to put forward your ingenious thoughts and let your imagination
soar. It is a battle of grey cells and wit where insanity is sane.
\nParticipate and be a part of an astounding event – My Amazing Discovery. Give a presentation on
what your idea is, why is it out-of-the-box and not easy to implement, yet why you think it is sheer
brilliance! A platform to prove technology starts with MAD people and their MAD ideas!\n\n</string>
    <string name="mad_structure">1. Proposed concept should be innovative and original.
\n\n2. A soft copy of your abstract (about 250-300 words) should be mailed to
madtalks.credenz17@gmail.com
\n\n3. The soft copy must be in *.pdf format.
\n\n4. Summaries will be evaluated by judges and 10 (+3 waiting) entries will be qualified for the nextround.
\n\n5. The finalists have to prepare a presentation of about 6-7 minutes (maximum time limit) that will
be presented during Credenz\'17 before a panel of judges.
\n\n6. The presentation will be followed by a question - answer session based on the proposed idea.
\n\n7. Teams will be evaluated based on their performance in the Presentation and Q/A round.
\nNOTE: LCD projector and Laptop will be provided.\n\n</string>
    <string name="mad_rules">1. A team of maximum 3 candidates pursuing undergraduate/postgraduate/junior college course are
allowed to participate.
\n\n2. All the participants should bring their receipts and college I-cards. Those without I-cards will not
be permitted and their team will be disqualified.\n\n</string>
    <string name="mad_judging">1. Originality and usability of the idea/plan (prime importance).
\n\n2. The hypothesis of the plan is extremely essential and should be scientifically correct.
\n\n3. Oratory and presentation skills of the participants.
\n\n4. The judges\' decision will be final and binding on all.\n\n</string>

    <string name="mad_coord1">Kritika Patade</string>
    <string name="mad_coord1_contact">+91 8805293402</string>
    <string name="mad_coord2">Himanshu Mithawala</string>
    <string name="mad_coord2_contact">+91 9028097725</string>
    <string name="mad_email">madtalks.credenz17@gmail.com</string>



    <!--NTH-->
    <string name="nth_intro">Hook onto Network Treasure Hunt, an online treasure hunt where participants follow clues and visit
different websites to solve riddles. Solve a series of strategic clues to complete the track and win
prizes. Decrypt the clues, follow the trail and race to the finish to win exciting goodies! This is your
chance to challenge your technical skills. So go on, login and be Sherlock for a day!\n\n</string>
    <string name="nth_rules">1.To start your hunt, go to www.credenz.info
\n\n2.Register to get your NTH username.
\n\n3.You will be directed to the starting page of the hunt.
\n\n4.To advance, crack the question, and put the answer in the URL:
\nFROM\nhttp://www.nth.credenz.info/question.php
\nTO\nhttp://www.nth.credenz.info/answer.php\n\n
\n\n5. You need Google by your side to solve many questions. Of course, that is where you search for
everything you don\'t know.
\n\n6. Check the source of the pages, you will get some important clues for hunting further. The titles
may also give you clues.
\n\n7. Most importantly, do not forget to have fun!\n\n</string>
    <string name="nth_structure">1. There will be two Network Treasure Hunts, three and one week respectively before Credenz\'17.
\n\n2. Both the Treasure Hunts are independent. There will be separate winners for both the Treasure
Hunts.
\n\n3. It consists of 30 to 50 levels each.
\n\n4. To go to the next level, you need to crack the present level in any possible way.\n\n</string>
    <string name="nth_judging">The person who cracks the highest number of levels wins. In case of a tie, the one who
reached that level first is the winner.\n\n</string>

    <string name="nth_coord1">Mohit Agrawal</string>
    <string name="nth_coord1_contact">+91 9028608363</string>
    <string name="nth_coord2">Sharveya Baxi</string>
    <string name="nth_coord2_contact">+91 7720008920</string>
    <string name="nth_email">nth.credenz2017@gmail.com</string>


    <!--Pixelate-->
    <string name="pixelate_intro">Plot the pixels of your imagination on the virtual canvas! If you think you can carve your message
with the fusion of colours, designs, words culminating into an elegant art, here is your chance.
Integrate your creativity with technology and paint your ideas!\n\n</string>
    <string name="pixelate_rules">1. A team of maximum two members pursuing undergraduate courses is allowed.
\n\n2. Registration fee is Rs.150 per team for Non-IEEE members and Rs. 120 per
team for IEEE members.
\n\n3. Every team should bring their own laptops on the day of the event.
\n\n4. All the participants should bring receipt and valid I-cards while coming for the contest. No one
without I-card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified.\n\n</string>
    <string name="pixelate_structure">ROUND 1:
\n\n1. Each team shall design a promotional poster based on the given theme which will be declared on
our website ONE month before the event.
\n\n2. The date for sending the poster will be declared on the website.
\n\n3. The designs should be submitted in *.psd,*.cdr, *.ai, etc format.
\n\n4. The design submitted should not be flattened.
\n\n5. The brushes and fonts used should be mentioned in the documentation.
\n\n6. Any external source or images used should also be included in the documentation.
\n\n\nROUND 2:
\n\n1. The teams shall be given a topic to design a poster, on the spot.
\n\n2. The time allotted for this round will be 3 hours.
\n\n3. You can use the internet for 20 minutes during the competition. Specific time will be allotted for
the same.
\n\n4. You are allowed to get your own brushes, fonts and textures. However, all this will be checked
prior to you starting the competition.\n\n</string>
    <string name="pixelate_judging">1. Creativity and originality of the design.
\n\n2. Distinct features incorporated in the design.
\n\n3. Persuasiveness of the design, i.e. the efficiency of the design to convey the required message.
\n\n4. Photoshop skills.
\n\n5. Layering and masking.
\n\n6. The decision of the judges will be final and shall be respected.\n\n</string>
    <string name="pixelate_question">
        Since ages, humans have been inventing amenities to ease their hard work and lead a comfortable
        life. Throughout these ages, these amenities have eased our work for us. However in recent
        times, the roles seemed to have reversed.
        \nFrom placing our beds near a charging socket to compromising the privacy of people by mass
        surveillance to feed our advanced AI. This just indicates that a new form of Slavery is on the rise.
        \n\nDesign a poster to depict how the present man is unknowingly giving rise to this modern slavery.
        \n\nCanvas size for poster should be 18” x 12” (landscape or portrait).
        \n\nEmail your posters at pixelate.credenz17@gmail.com in raw formats (*.psd, *.cdr, *.ai).
        \n\nLast date of Submission is 10th September 2017.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="pixelate_coord1">Sanket Kokane</string>
    <string name="pixelate_coord1_contact">+91 7620186985</string>
    <string name="pixelate_coord2">Shivani Firke</string>
    <string name="pixelate_coord2_contact">+91 7350747840</string>
    <string name="pixelate_email">pixelate.credenz17@gmail.com</string>

    <!--B-Plan-->
    <string name="bplan_intro">This event is an opportunity for young minds who aim to
become entrepreneurs in the near future, to THINK big and prove it to the world. It will certainly be
a good opportunity to have discussions with students, just as ambitious as you, and the well-learned
people who can provide valuable guidance. Come, step forward and present your innovative ideas
to a distinguished panel of judges.\n\n</string>
    <string name="bplan_rules">1. A maximum of three candidates per plan pursuing undergraduate/graduate/postgraduate
program at their institution will be allowed per team.
\n\n2. Proposed business plan should not be in violation of any intellectual property rights.
\n\n3. Registration fee is 150/- per team for Non-IEEE members and 120/- per team for IEEE members.
\n\n4. All the participants should bring receipt and valid I-cards while coming for the contest. No one
without I-card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified.\n\n</string>
    <string name="bplan_structure">1. At stage 1, the soft copy of the abstract (summary) should be submitted to
bplan.credenz17@gmail.com
\n\n2. The Soft copy should be a .pdf file.
\n\n3. Executive Summaries will be evaluated by judges and 7 drafts (+3 waiting) will be shortlisted
        for the next stage.
for the next stage takes place.
\n\n4. Each team will be given 12 minutes in the final round to present their B-PLAN in College
Auditorium in front of panel of judges and audience. A warning bell will be given at 10 minutes and
a final 2 minutes thereafter.
\n\n5. The presentation would be followed by a question-answer session where they would be
questioned on different hurdles, opportunities and obstacles at various points.
\n\n6. The main stress during question-answer session would be given on feasibility and Exit Plan.\n\n</string>
    <string name="bplan_judging">1. Innovation involved in the development of the idea and its practicality.
\n\n2. Originality and Patentability.
\n\n3. Technical feasibility.
\n\n4. Implementation of the product.
\n\n5. Cost efficiency (if relevant).
\n\n6. Superiority of the product over existing products in market.
\n\n7. Participants will be judged on the basis of their business acumen and on how sustainable and
innovative their solution is.
\n\n8. The decision of the judges will be final and shall be respected.\n\n</string>

    <string name="bplan_coord1">Ankit Hiware</string>
    <string name="bplan_coord1_contact">+91 8888051821</string>
    <string name="bplan_coord2">Tanmay Bagdiya</string>
    <string name="bplan_coord2_contact">+91 8275854193</string>
    <string name="bplan_email">bplan.credenz17@gmail.com</string>


    <!--Cretronix-->
    <string name="cretronix_intro">An electronics based competition which tests the participant\'s theoretical and practical knowledge
        (all students from FE to BE.)\n\n</string>
    <string name="cretronix_rules">1. The teams will be shortlisted for the next round based on their scores in the previous round.
If a tie takes place, the time factor and accuracy will be taken into consideration.
\n\n2. The event will be conducted in two levels:
\nJunior level
\nSenior level
\n\n3. I-card and receipt is compulsory.
\n\n4. Electronic gadgets are not allowed.\n\n</string>
    <string name="cretronix_structure">
Junior level:
\n1st round:
\nSection 1: Single choice MCQ\'s.
\nSection 2: Crossword
\n\n2nd round:
\nThe participants will be given a circuit with bugs on a breadboard or a general-purpose PCB along
with input and expected output conditions. They have to find the bugs and debug it to obtain the
correct expected output.
\n\n3rd round: Circuit Designing and implementation
\nThe participants will be given a problem statement and they are supposed to implement the solution
with the help of hardware. They will also be provided with input-output data, for which they have to
build the required circuit.
\n\nSenior level:
\n1st round:
\nSection 1: Single choice MCQ\'s.
\nSection 2: Crossword
\n\n2nd round:\nHARDWARE/SOFTWARE DEBUGGING
\nThe participants will be given a problem statement for which they are supposed to implement the
solution for HARDWARE/SOFTWARE DEBUGGING. They will also be provided with input-
output conditions. Participants will have to write a code for SOFTWARES.
\n\n3rd round:\nCIRCUIT DESIGN AND IMPLEMENTATION
\nThe participants will be given a problem statement for which they are supposed to implement the
solution with the help of hardware/software (Proteus).They will also be provided with input-output
waveforms for which they have to build the desired circuit.\n\n</string>
    <string name="cretronix_judging">It will test your basic knowledge of electronics and practical implementation.\n\nTotal Shortlisted teams for 2nd round - 12
\n\nTotal Shortlisted teams for 3rd round - 6\n\n</string>

    <string name="cretronix_coord1">Kartik Sahasrabudhe</string>
    <string name="cretronix_coord1_contact">+91 9730469993</string>
    <string name="cretronix_coord2"></string>
    <string name="cretronix_coord2_contact"></string>
    <string name="cretronix_email">cretronix.credenz17@gmail.com</string>


    <!--Wallstreet-->
    <string name="wall_intro">Ever wondered how those blue collars sitting in their corner office make deals worth over billions
of dollars? Also, ever wondered why is there so much chaos due to the fluctuations in Sensex?
Here is a virtual stock market to get a glimpse of everything that happens on Dalal Street.\n\n</string>
    <string name="wall_rules">1.Every Participating candidate should be pursuing Undergraduate/Graduate courses.
\n\n2.Registration fee is Rs.50 per individual for Non-IEEE member and Rs.40 for IEEE member.
\n\n3.All the participants should bring valid I-cards while coming for the contest. No one without
I-card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified.\n\n</string>
    <string name="wall_structure">1. The event will be conducted within PICT campus on all 3 days.
\n\n2. Every participant will be given virtual money to trade on our virtual stock market.
\n\n3. The event will be conducted via our App/Website.
\n\n4. Mock NEWS will be flashed regarding listed companies and their sectors based on which
participants will buy/sell stocks to ultimately become the biggest gainer.
\n\n5. Concepts such as IPO, short selling and high Frequency Trading will be inculcated within
the event.\n\n</string>
    <string name="wall_judging">Top 3 participants with Highest Capital at the end of Day 3 will be declared as winners.\n\n</string>

    <string name="wall_coord1">Atharva Gomekar</string>
    <string name="wall_coord1_contact">+91 7030447477</string>
    <string name="wall_coord2">Vaibhav Yende</string>
    <string name="wall_coord2_contact">+91 8888310905</string>
    <string name="wall_email">wallstreet.credenz17@gmail.com</string>


    <!--Reverse Coding-->
    <string name="rc_intro">Given some sequence of steps, writing a code and getting the output is pretty easy! Want to try a
reverse way? If given some input and output, can you find the logic and sequence? Focusing less on
concepts, all you need is your logical skill to decipher this "Black Box". Reverse Coding is a logical
event which tests your basic logical skills along with pattern analysis and recognition as you play
with the code. So, get ready to reverse code in Credenz\'17!\n\n</string>
    <string name="rc_structure">1. There are two rounds:
\na. Logic Round.
\nb. Decipher and Code Round.
\n\n2. Logic round consists of Logical questions which can be solved by coding.
\n\n3. In the Decipher and coding round, the participants have to write the code for pattern that maps
input to output.
\n\n4. The event will be conducted in two categories, Junior level(First and Second year) and Senior
level(Third and Fourth year).\n\n</string>
    <string name="rc_rules">1. A maximum of 2 candidates pursuing undergraduate program at their institution are allowed per
team.
\n\n2. Registration fees is Rs.70/- per team for Non-IEEE members and Rs.50/- per team for IEEE
members.
\n\n3. All the participants should bring their receipt and valid I-cards while coming for the contest. A
participant without an I-card will NOT be allowed for the contest and the respective team will be
disqualified.
\n\n4. Marking scheme will be declared on spot.\n\n</string>
    <string name="rc_judging">1. The competition will test the participants\' logical and coding skills.
\n\n2. Time and cost efficiency of the code will be tested in round 2.\n\n</string>

    <string name="rc_coord1">Chinmay Ingle</string>
    <string name="rc_coord1_contact">+91 8975085233</string>
    <string name="rc_coord2">Ajay Sabale</string>
    <string name="rc_coord2_contact">+91 8600070474</string>
    <string name="rc_email">reversecode.credenz17@gmail.com</string>


    <!--Contraption-->
    <string name="contraption_intro">Have you ever wondered how to apply toothpaste on your brush in 20 steps?
        Ever wondered how to light a candle in 30 steps? Contraption is all about complexifying
        the simplest of things you see around yourself. Its whole essence lies in a perfectly
        balanced mix of innovation, creativity and relevance which guarantees profound entertainment.\n\n</string>
    <string name="contraption_rules"> 1. A team of max. four members is allowed to participate.
        \n\n2. Registration fees is Rs.200/- per team for Non-IEEE members and Rs.180/- per team for IEEE
        members.
        \n\n3. Machine should be of dimensions 8ft x 8ft x 8ft (maximum).
        \n\n4. Minimum 10 steps should be involved to complete the task otherwise team will be disqualified.
        However there is no constrain on maximum no. of steps.
        \n\n5. Minimum 4 different energy conversion should be implemented in machine. Otherwise team will be disqualified.
        \n\n6. Machine should perform the task in maximum of 4 minutes.
        \n\n7. Machine should not take support of any of four walls and ceiling.
        \n\n8. Teams have to submit abstract and flowchart in prescribed format well before the first round.
        \n\n9. Maximum of three trials/chances will be given to any team. For every other chance/trial
        there will be deduction of points.
        \n\n10. For every next chance reset time of 15 mins will be given to team.
        \n\n11. Only one team member is allowed to interact with the machine once the evaluation has begun.
        This includes resetting the machine during the run. This means that only one person will be
        allowed inside the arena. However, if the team goes for another run, the restriction of one
        person inside the arena is uplifted until the machine is ready for the other run.
        \n\n12. That person will explain about the machine and each step going on to judges.
        \n\n13. Each step in the machine should be considered as the transfer of one energy into another.
        A step is considered to accomplish when there is energy transformation. For example: a ball rolling
        down a wedge and hitting a domino is consider a step. In this the potential energy of
        ball is transformed into kinetic energy while coming down and when it hits the domino, it transfers
        its energy to domino.
        \n\n14. Identical transfers of energy in succession should be considered one step. For eg., a set
        of dominos falling into each other should be considered one step. While technically each
        single domino falling is a step, stating one hundred steps for hundred dominos is repetitive
        and against the spirit of Rube Goldberg.
        \n\n15. You can use any material for making of your machine provided in any case , they does not
        lead damage to arena and other machines. Otherwise it will lead to disqualification of team.
        \n\n16. Use of hazardous materials, gases or explosives is strictly prohibited.
        However you can use matchstick if required, provided it does not damage the arena and any other
        Machine.
        \n\n17. We will not provide you any material for making your Machine. However basic stationary
        materials will be provided to you.
        \n\n18. If required extension boards will be provided to you. But we would really appreciate if
        you bring of your own.
        \n\n19. Bring two copies of your abstract on the day of the event.
        \n\n20. No live animal should be used.
        \n\n21. Organizers have the right to change a rule or all if they feel.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="contraption_structure">
        Round 1
        \n1. Problem statement will be released on the website 15 days prior to the event.
        \n\n2.Participants have to mail their abstract at contraption.credenz17@gmail.com.
        \n\n\nRound 2
        \n1. Best abstracts will be shortlisted from the first round.
        \n\n2. These teams will be allowed to come to college and demonstrate their machine and
        present their innovation.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="contraption_judging">Judging criteria is as follows:
        \n\n1. Design of your machine
    \n\n2. Number of steps involved in it
    \n\n3. Number of different types of energy conversions involved
    \n\n4. Aesthetic of the machine
    \n\n5. Presentation
    \n\n6. Innovation
    \n\n7. Elementary knowledge of applied physics will be tested.
    \n\n8. Innovative and team management skills will also be tested.\n\n
</string>
    <string name="contraption_question">
        1. Design a machine of (8*8*8) cubic ft that plays Sa-Re-Ga-Ma-Pa-Dha-Ni-Sa at
        different stages till the final step.
        \n\n2. During execution, your machine should display CREDENZ \'17 at any intermediate state.
        \n\n3. Maximum execution time is 4 minutes.
        \n\n4. Email your abstract at contraption.credenz17@gmail.com
        \n\n5. Last date of Submission is 9th September 2017.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="contraption_coord1">Nakul Thombare</string>
    <string name="contraption_coord1_contact">+91 9403400844</string>
    <string name="contraption_coord2">Prathamesh Jadhav</string>
    <string name="contraption_coord2_contact">+91 8055851129</string>
    <string name="contraption_email">contraption.credenz17@gmail.com</string>


    <!--Paper Presentation-->
    <string name="paper_intro">
        It is always said that knowledge is not something to be confined to oneself, but something
        to be shared as much as possible. One of the most popular events of Credenz, Paper Presentation
        gives a platform to undergraduate/ postgraduate students to present technical papers. So, here
        is your chance to challenge your own skills of research and put forth your ideas on technology
        in front of an experienced panel of judges.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="paper_rules">
        1. A team of maximum three candidates pursuing undergraduate / postgraduate program are allowed.
        \n\n2. Registration fees is Rs.200/- per team for Non-IEEE members and Rs.180/- per team for IEEE
        members.
        \n\n3. All the participants should bring valid I-cards while coming for the contest. Anyone
        without an I-card will not be allowed to contest and will lead to immediate disqualification
        of the respective team.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="paper_structure">
        1. Only soft copy i.e. a .pdf file, of the paper and abstract should be submitted. The paper
        should not exceed more than 6 pages.
        \n\n2. Soft copy of the technical paper and the abstract should be mailed to paper.credenz17@gmail.com.
        \n\n3. The paper must strictly adhere to the IEEE format.
        \n\n4. Authors will get 15 minutes to deliver a presentation on their topic followed by a question - answer session.
        \n\n5. The presentation should be in power point format (.ppt or .pptx).\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="paper_judging">
        1. Oratory and Presentation skills will be of prime importance.
        \n\n2. Relevance of the content in context with the chosen topic.
        \n\n3. Judge\'s decision will be final and binding on all.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="paper_coord1">Anshika Agrawal</string>
    <string name="paper_coord1_contact">+91 9920619918</string>
    <string name="paper_coord2">Viram Shah</string>
    <string name="paper_coord2_contact">+91 9921388069</string>
    <string name="paper_email">paper.credenz17@gmail.com</string>


    <!--QUIZ-->
    <string name="quiz_intro">
        There is no measure for intelligence and wisdom. The closest we could reach was by defining
        an IQ. Fortunately each of us is gifted with this feature. The question is, to what extent
        do we possess it.
        \nDiscover the scope of this feature by Setting out on a voyage through a sea of mind-boggling
        questions captained by a witty quizmaster.\n\nThe Quiz is divided into following three categories held on three different days:
        \n1. General Quiz: It includes everything from robotics to politics. Test your GK!
        \n2. MELA Quiz: Movies Entertainment Literature and Arts (MELA), is all set to test your knowledge
        of literature, arts and entertainment. If you are an entertainment lover, this is for you!
        \n3. Biz Tech Quiz: If you are passionate about marketing, economics and business, then Biz Tech
        is the ultimate questionnaire you need to answer to test your knowledge.
        \n\nSo brace yourself for captivating this intriguing questionnaire whose answers might just be
        lying somewhere at the back of your mind.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="quiz_rules">
        1. A maximum of two candidates pursuing under graduate/graduate program at their institution will be allowed per team.
        \n\n2. Registration fees is Rs.50/- per team, per quiz for Non-IEEE members and Rs.40/- per team per quiz for IEEE
        members.
        \n\n3. Teams can register at desks put up at various colleges in and around Pune. No one without
        I-card will be allowed for the contest and the team will be disqualified. A team has to register
        itself at registration desk at time of event, one hour prior to the event.
        \n\n4. Teams may re-register for another time slot.
        \n\n5. All the participants should bring receipt and valid I-cards while coming for the event.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="quiz_structure">
        1. There will be two rounds - one elimination round and one final round.
        \n\n2. Details about structure of quiz will be provided at the time of the event.
        \n\n3. Quiz masters\' decision will be final on all matters.
        \n\n4. Round 1 will be elimination round with no negative marking and round 2 will be conducted by the Quiz Master.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="quiz_judging">
        Round 1:
        \n1. For this round 25 questions will be asked.
        \n2. Top 6 teams will be short listed for the second round.
        \n\nRound 2:
        \nThere will be 6 teams in the final round. The round will be conducted by the Quiz Master.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="quiz_coord1">Atharva Gomekar</string>
    <string name="quiz_coord1_contact">+91 7030447477</string>
    <string name="quiz_coord2">Vishva Iyer</string>
    <string name="quiz_coord2_contact">+91 9422028395</string>
    <string name="quiz_email">quiz.credenz17@gmail.com</string>


    <!--Software Development-->
    <string name="softdev_intro">
        Software Development will be an Application Development Competition, android or desktop, with
        no restriction on the choice of programming language used. You can use ANY existing programming
        language(s) to make your application. The application will be judged by experts in the software
        industry.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="softdev_rules">
        1. Maximum of three people in a team.
        \n\n2. The competition consists of two levels-
        \nJunior level (For First and Second Year students)
        \nSenior level (For Third and Fourth Year students)
        \n\n3. All the participants should bring receipt and valid I-cards while coming for the contest.
        A single team member without an I-card will result in the disqualification of the entire team.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="softdev_structure">
        1. Participants will have to showcase their software applications on the day of event(i.e. Credenz \'17).
        \n\n2. Winners will be declared once all applications have been reviewed by judges.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="softdev_question">
        Junior Category:
        \nDesign and implement an application based on one of the following topics:
        \n\n1. Design and implement an application which helps users find out about the various events
        (eg. Stand up, dramas, flee markets, concerts, sports events)taking place in a city(eg. Pune).
        The categories of events can be decided by the developer.
        \n\n2. Design and implement an application for book lovers which would enable them to lend and
        borrow books. Users should be able to enlist the books they are willing to lend. Also, they
        should be able to search for books available for borrowing. Additional features are left up
        to the participants discretion.
        \n\n3. Design and implement an application for artists and art lovers. The application will be a
        platform for artists such as painters, sculptors, musicians, graphic designer etc to showcase
        their talents in their respective fields. The app also enables art connoisseurs to view the
        art, contact the artist and buy their art. Authentication and piracy related issues should
        be taken into consideration by the developer.
        \n\n4. Design and implement an app of your choice.
        \n\n\nSenior Category:
        \nDesign and implement an application based on one of the following topics:
        \n\n1. Sentiment analysis.
        \n\n2. Women safety.
        \n\n3. Using technology to enhance Road transportation.
        \n\n4. Computational and data security.
        \n\n5. Neural Networks.
        \n\n6. Image processing.
        \n\n7. Social Media.
        \n\n8. Mobile Computing.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="softdev_judging">
        Criteria for Judging would consist of multiple parameters:
        \n\n1. User Interface
        \n\n2. User friendliness
        \n\n3. Deployment Scenarios
        \n\n4. Presentability
        \n\n5. Scenario Adaptability
        \n\n6. Feature Richness
        \n\n7. And a few more.
        \n\nScenario Adaptability: You might be asked to clarify the use of your application in certain
        scenarios, say "What if this software needs to be used in a Library? Or on a Cruiser?", "Can you
        elaborate on how that can be accomplished?", "What if this needs to be deployed in Software
        Company\'s office? At a manager\'s desk?"\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="softdev_coord1">Sabarinath S.</string>
    <string name="softdev_coord1_contact">+91 9405296837</string>
    <string name="softdev_coord2">Rutuja Patil</string>
    <string name="softdev_coord2_contact">+91 9834717070</string>
    <string name="softdev_email">softwaredevelopment.credenz17@gmail.com</string>


    <!--Xodia-->
    <string name="xodia_intro">
        The Bot Game is a game between two programmed codes. The code can be programmed in either
        C/C++/Java/Python. Two bots will play against each other in a match, which is carried out
        by a programmed Game-Judge. The details of the game will be put up on the XOdia\'17
        website during Credenz.
        \n\nRegistration is free of cost.
        \n\nTime period for programming the bot: 15 days.
        \n\nAllowed Languages: C/C++/Java/Python\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="xodia_rules">
        1. A single person is allowed to participate, no teams will be entertained and may lead to disqualification.
        \n\n2. Participants need to provide required information on and as and when required.
        \n\n3. Any malicious activity encountered by the bot will lead to disqualification.
        \n\n4. Participants are allowed to send modified/corrected codes before the last date of submission
        (Submission dates will be released on the website). Any request for modification of code
        will not be entertained after that.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="xodia_structure">
        1. Submission Procedure: The programmed bots have to be submitted on the website by the last
        day of submission given on the website.
        \n\n2. The rules of the game and details of the interaction of the bot will be with the game
        description on the Website.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="xodia_judging">
        The rules for scoring and deciding the winner will be mentioned on the website, with the game details.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="xodia_coord1">Faraz Saifulla</string>
    <string name="xodia_coord1_contact">+91 9145382864</string>
    <string name="xodia_coord2">Sayali Deshpande</string>
    <string name="xodia_coord2_contact">+91 9049541066</string>
    <string name="xodia_email">xodia.credenz17@gmail.com</string>







    <string name="ping_info"><b>PICT IEEE Newsletter Group</b>
        \n\nP.I.N.G. is the official technical magazine of PISB published biannually. P.I.N.G. serves
        as a platform for individuals to portray their technical ingenuity. It highlights articles
        on cutting-edge technology from technocrats all around the globe including students,
        industrialists and faculty members. It also features interviews of distinguished personalities
        in various technical domains. P.I.N.G. aims at keeping its readers up to date on recent
        developments in technology and helps them extrapolate their perceptions to contemporary ideas
        of modernisation.\n\nWith the imminent Issue 13.1, get ready to be PING\'d!
    </string>
    <string name="pingissueslink"></string>

    <string name="btn_regist">Register</string>
</resources>
